{
  "Poetry": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "Question": "山暖已无梅可折",
      "Answer": [ "好竹连山觉笋香", "江清独有蟹堪持", "春近录苗嫩不蔹", "碧油煎出嫩黄深" ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "Question": "日啖荔枝三百颗",
      "Answer": [ "不辞长做岭南人", "一夜征人尽望乡", "新津韭黄天下无", "但愿长醉不愿醒" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 3,
      "Question": "秦烹惟羊羹",
      "Answer": [ "把酒话桑麻", "新炊间黄梁", "陇馔有熊腊", "蜀酒浓无敌" ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 4,
      "Question": "长江绕郭知鱼美",
      "Answer": [ "好竹连山觉笋香", "糁羹珍美胜羔豚", "脍飞金盘白雪高", "一瓯冰水和梅汤" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 5,
      "Question": "新津韭黄天下无",
      "Answer": [ "更为吴酸作解嘲", "卢橘杨梅次第新", "色如鹅黄三尺余", "江米如珠井水淘" ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 6,
      "Question": "东门彘肉更奇绝",
      "Answer": [ "晴窗细乳戏分茶", "象箸水盘物物佳", "滑欲流匙香满屋", "脍飞金盘白雪高" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 7,
      "Question": "何时一饱与子同",
      "Answer": [ "更煎士茗浮甘菊", "烂煮春风三月初", "兰陵美酒郁金香", "清香不断鼎烹龙" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 8,
      "Question": "紫驼之峰出翠釜",
      "Answer": [ "炊成不减雕胡美", "美人纤手炙鱼头", "矮纸斜行闲作草", "水精之盘行素鳞" ],
      "correct": 4
    },
    {
      "number": 9,
      "Question": "青青竹笋迎船出",
      "Answer": [ "白白红鱼入馔来", "大如苋实白如玉", "王四酒家风味好", "夜半酣酒江月下" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 10,
      "Question": "蜀酒浓无敌",
      "Answer": [ "但闻人语响", " 江鱼美可求", "醢酱点橙薤", "未解忆长安" ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 11,
      "Question": "鲜鲫食丝脍",
      "Answer": [ "吴溪紫蟹肥", "香芹碧涧羹", "把酒话桑麻", "还来就菊花" ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 12,
      "Question": "问答未及已",
      "Answer": [ "儿女罗酒浆", "邀我至田家", "空有羡鱼情", "茱萸插玳筵" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 13,
      "Question": "夜雨剪春韭",
      "Answer": [ "把酒话桑麻", "邀我至田家", "新炊间黄梁", "同是宦游人" ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 14,
      "Question": "甲第纷纷厌梁肉",
      "Answer": [ "广文先生食不足", "丰年留客足鸡豚", "一瓯冰水和梅汤", "下官亦为啖鱼回" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 15,
      "Question": "饔子左右挥双刀",
      "Answer": [ "桂花香馅裹胡桃", "时绕麦田求野荠", "脍飞金盘白雪高", "采掇归来便堪煮" ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 16,
      "Question": "夜半酣酒江月下",
      "Answer": [ "美人纤手炙鱼头", "瓦壶天水菊花茶", "初游唐安饭薏米", "罗浮山下四时春" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 17,
      "Question": "扬州鲜笋趁鲥鱼",
      "Answer": [ "烂煮春风三月初", "初游唐安饭薏米", "莫笑农家腊酒浑", "清香不断鼎烹龙" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 18,
      "Question": "惟有莼鲈堪漫吃",
      "Answer": [ "霜余蔬甲淡中甜", "美人纤手炙鱼头", "美人纤手炙鱼头", "下官亦为啖鱼回" ],
      "correct": 4
    },
    {
      "number": 19,
      "Question": "天上苏陀供",
      "Answer": [ "悬知未易同", "空有羡鱼情", "阴阳割昏晓", "齐鲁青未了" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 20,
      "Question": "年来传得甜羹法",
      "Answer": [ "但闻人语响", " 更为吴酸作解嘲", "家书抵万金", "未解忆长安" ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 21,
      "Question": "东门买彘骨",
      "Answer": [ "清泉石上流", "醢酱点橙薤", "隔水问樵夫", "还来就菊花" ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 22,
      "Question": "蒸鸡最知名",
      "Answer": [ "美不数鱼鳖", "一片孤城万仞山", "客舍青青柳色青", "轻舟已过万重山" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 23,
      "Question": "霜余蔬甲淡中甜",
      "Answer": [ "把酒话桑麻", "邀我至田家", "春近录苗嫩不蔹", "同是宦游人" ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 24,
      "Question": "大如苋实白如玉",
      "Answer": [ "滑欲流匙香满屋", "端居耻圣明", "同是宦游人", "更上一层楼" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 25,
      "Question": "采掇归来便堪煮",
      "Answer": [ "一夜征人尽望乡", "白云千载空悠悠", "半铢盐酪不须添", "轻舟已过万重山" ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 26,
      "Question": "初游唐安饭薏米",
      "Answer": [ "炊成不减雕胡美", "一览众山小", "隔水问樵夫", "端居耻圣明" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 27,
      "Question": "白菜青盐糙米饭",
      "Answer": [ "瓦壶天水菊花茶", "凭君传语报平安", "一夜征人尽望乡", "一夜征人尽望乡" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 28,
      "Question": "秀色可怜刀切肉",
      "Answer": [ "人生得意须尽欢", "但愿长醉不愿醒", "水精之盘行素鳞", "清香不断鼎烹龙" ],
      "correct": 4
    },
    {
      "number": 29,
      "Question": "西塞山前白鹭飞",
      "Answer": [ "桃花流水鳜鱼肥", "空有羡鱼情", "阴阳割昏晓", "齐鲁青未了" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 30,
      "Question": "越浦黄柑嫩",
      "Answer": [ "邀我至田家", " 吴溪紫蟹肥", "青青高槐叶", "芍药和金鼎" ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 31,
      "Question": "江上往来人",
      "Answer": [ "清泉石上流", "但爱鲈鱼美", "隔水问樵夫", "还来就菊花" ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 32,
      "Question": "罗浮山下四时春",
      "Answer": [ "卢橘杨梅次第新", "紫驼之峰出翠釜", "客舍青青柳色新", "卢橘杨梅次第新" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 33,
      "Question": "一骑红尘妃子笑",
      "Answer": [ "时绕麦田求野荠", "夜半酣酒江月下", "无人知是荔枝来", "采掇归来便堪煮" ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 34,
      "Question": "莫笑农家腊酒浑",
      "Answer": [ "丰年留客足鸡豚", "扬州鲜笋趁鲥鱼", "西塞山前白鹭飞", "烂煮春风三月初" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 35,
      "Question": "草卧夕阳牛犊健",
      "Answer": [ "南烹北果聚君家", "夜打春雷第一声", "菊留秋色蟹螯肥", "瓦壶天水菊花茶" ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 36,
      "Question": "王四酒家风味好",
      "Answer": [ "黄鸡白酒嫩菠青", "一览众山小", "隔水问樵夫", "端居耻圣明" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 37,
      "Question": "桂花香馅裹胡桃",
      "Answer": [ "江米如珠井水淘", "饔子左右挥双刀", "惟有莼鲈堪漫吃", "脍飞金盘白雪高" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 38,
      "Question": "汤饼一杯银线乱",
      "Answer": [ "人生得意须尽欢", "但愿长醉不愿醒", "水精之盘行素鳞", "蒌蒿如箸玉簪横" ],
      "correct": 4
    },
    {
      "number": 39,
      "Question": "青青高槐叶",
      "Answer": [ "采掇付中厨", "空有羡鱼情", "香饭兼苞芦", "茱萸插玳筵" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 40,
      "Question": "碧鲜俱照箸",
      "Answer": [ "悬知未易同", " 香饭兼苞芦", "夜雨剪春韭", "未解忆长安" ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 41,
      "Question": "兰陵美酒郁金香",
      "Answer": [ "秀色可怜刀切肉", "玉碗盛来琥珀光", "卢橘杨梅次第新", "王四酒家风味好" ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 42,
      "Question": "矮纸斜行闲作草",
      "Answer": [ "晴窗细乳戏分茶", "采掇归来便堪煮", "半铢盐酪不须添", "炊成不减雕胡美" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 43,
      "Question": "铜碗声声街里唤",
      "Answer": [ "霜余蔬甲淡中甜", "蒌蒿如箸玉簪横", "一瓯冰水和梅汤", "碧油煎出嫩黄深" ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 44,
      "Question": "纤手搓来玉色匀",
      "Answer": [ "碧油煎出嫩黄深", "紫驼之峰出翠釜", "残雪初消荠满园", "清香不断鼎烹龙" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 45,
      "Question": "夜打春雷第一声",
      "Answer": [ "初游唐安饭薏米", "罗浮山下四时春", "满山新笋玉棱棱", "扬州鲜笋趁鲥鱼" ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 46,
      "Question": "紫驼之峰出翠釜",
      "Answer": [ "水精之盘行素鳞", "玉碗盛来琥珀光", "菊留秋色蟹螯肥", "桃花流水鳜鱼肥" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 47,
      "Question": "南烹北果聚君家",
      "Answer": [ "象箸水盘物物佳", "半铢盐酪不须添", "满山新笋玉棱棱", "炊成不减雕胡美" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 48,
      "Question": "时绕麦田求野荠",
      "Answer": [ "不辞长做岭南人", "江清独有蟹堪持", "水精之盘行素鳞", "强为僧舍煮山羹" ],
      "correct": 4
    },
    {
      "number": 49,
      "Question": "残雪初消荠满园",
      "Answer": [ "糁羹珍美胜羔豚", "更煎士茗浮甘菊", "更为吴酸作解嘲", "新津韭黄天下无" ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 50,
      "Question": "芍药和金鼎",
      "Answer": [ "青青高槐叶", " 茱萸插玳筵", "陇馔有熊腊", "未解忆长安" ],
      "correct": 2
    }
  ]
}